#### Contact

noellador@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/zubair-azimmiazi (LinkedIn) github.com/ZubairAzimMiazi (Portfolio)

#### Top Skills

Machine Learning
Computer Science
Management

# Zubair Azim Miazi

ML, Technology and Business Personnel, Adaptive. Dhaka

### Summary

Experienced with a demonstrated history of working in Computer and Software. Skilled in Machine learning, Technological Research, Advanced Research, Office Assistance and Management . Strong business and Analytical development professional with BSc focused in Computer Science from North South University.

## Experience

NSU ACM Student Chapter Probationary member October 2018 - Present (2 years 9 months) Dhaka, Bangladesh

IEEE NSU Student Branch- INSB Member June 2018 - Present (3 years 1 month)

#### Education

North South University

Bachelor of Science - BS, Computer Science · (2017 - 2020)

Dhanmondi Ideal College

Government laboratory High School